Nobody listened. Nobody cared. Until the night they went "Over the Edge"
Over the Edge is a crime, drama film directed by Jonathan Kaplan.
A group of bored teenagers rebel against authority
in the community of New Granada.
Carl, played by Michael Eric Kramer.
Cory, played by Pamela Ludwig.
Richie, played by Matt Dillon.
Mark, played by Vincent Spano.
Claude, played by Tom Fergus.
Doberman, played by Harry Northup.
Over the Edge is a 1979 American coming-of-age film directed
by Jonathan Kaplan and released in May 1979.
The film, based on actual events, had a limited theatrical
release but has since achieved cult film status.
It was Matt Dillon's film debut.
The film explores themes of rock 'n' roll, police
brutality, police, alcohol, boredom.
The tone is dark and emotional.